Narrator: 1
A: Hi, Kim. Listen, do you want come to the theatre in London this Saturday?
B: Saturday? I can’t – it’s my brother’s twenty-first birthday!
We’re having a big party at my parents’ house.
A: Oh, that sounds great!
Have a wonderful time – and say ‘Happy Birthday’ from me!
Narrator: 2
A: Are you in the office next week?
B: No, I’m on holiday.
A: Where are you going?
B: Australia!
A: Lucky you! When do you get back?
B: On the thirtieth.
A: Wow! That’s a long holiday.
B: Yeah, three weeks! I can’t wait.
Narrator: 3
A: You drink a lot of coffee!
B: Yes, this is my fifth this morning.
A: It’s not good for you, you know.
B: I know, but I can’t wake up without it.
Narrator: 4
A: Where’s the restaurant?
B: It’s not far. It’s on the corner of Park Avenue and fifty-third.
A: Great. See you there at seven thirty.
Narrator: 5
A: Good morning. I’m here to see Lynn Mody.
My name’s Graham Davies.
B: Just a moment, sir, I’ll give her a ring
…Is that Lynn? There’s a Mr Davies here to see you…That’s fine, sir.
Could you sign in here? Great.
You can go straight up. She’s on the sixth floor.
The lifts are just over there.
A: Many thanks.